Guide to the Queers for Economic Justice records, circa 2000-2014.
Queers for Economic Justice
- Series V. Project Files
  - Day of Action, 2005, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Queer History questions and answers (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Signed Race Forms, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Sex and Class Transgender (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Corporate Influence (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Class Roundtable, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Organizing in Working Class Community (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Access to Power (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Gay Agenda (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - General, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Training for Transformation (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Welfare Articles, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Outreach 2 Organizations (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Welfare Warriors forms/info (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Welfare Warriors planning committee, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Medicaid Information (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Fair Hearing Information (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Supportive Housing Rent Hikes, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Welfare and gift giving (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Packets and board members (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - What We Do (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - QEJ Literature (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Penelope's wors (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Beyond Same-Sex Marriage, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    Expenses for the summit
  - Public Policy Committee, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - QEJ Book (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Website Library, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - QEJ Legal Services, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - NYU packet, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Position Papers and Strategic Plans, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - United We Stand editorial, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - QEJ Booklet and information (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Shelter, Welfare, and Know Your Rights, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Welfare Warriors Leadership Course, from binder, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - Volunteer information packets (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - QEJ in the Media, from binder (Box 6, Folder 4-7)
  - The New York Blade, February, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Walmart free NYC (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - ED Search, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - QEJ Media and Articles, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Woodhill Sexual Freedom Alliance, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Brown University, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Kenyon Workplan, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - ED Transition/Needed from Kenyon, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - SAGE/AH, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - CLAGS/AH, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - NYWF/Sex Work, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - SEEDS (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - ASA Aging Piece (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Joseph's Book, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Vision Paper/workplan, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Workplace Bullying, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Workplan/BC/AH, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Suicide risk in LGBT Populations, Gender Identity Job Discrimination, Folders of QEJ donation forms, Bringing Spirituality Out of the Closet (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - New World Foundation (AH Comments), 2010-2011 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - National Latina Institute for Reproductive Health, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Search Committee A, B, C, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 28-31)
  - Suicide and LGBT Risk Papaer, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Discounted Jobs, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Felix, miscellaneous, 2010-2011 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - HIV Ban, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Trans, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Intern Packet (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Workshop packets and cards (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - QEJ Management letter, Financial statements, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Workers' Comp and Gov/Fed, 2007-2010 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - NYS Assembly and ESPA, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - NYS Office of Children and Family Services, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - State Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 43-44)
  - QEJ shelter groups, from binder, 2011-2012 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Dirk McCall LGBT Homeless Youth (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Richard Kim, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - DHS Domestic Partners (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Parade pictures and banner (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Series VI. Welfare Rights and Shelter Director
  A folder of photographs and the files of shelter director Jay Toole are included in the administrative records of QEJ’s Shelter project.
  - Manhattan Neighborhood Network files and video releases, from binder, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 21-22)
  - TANF information, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Vigil Permit, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Welfare City Policies, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Research Project, 2006-2007 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Welfare Warriors Research Collaborative, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Public Assistance (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Welfare Warriors flyers (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - WRN Information, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Organizing Committee, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Critical Resistance Campaign, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Public Assistance Information (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Summer interns, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Outreach team (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Homeless Shelter System flow charts and information (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - WEP Information (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - NGLTF blank survey, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Leadership Course Curriculum and Materials, 2000-2010 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Astraea award information, Arcus grant, 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - HRA Information (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Outreach information (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Leadership course application (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - WEJ Immigration project (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Outreach materials (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Video forms, general QEJ information (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Welfare Warriors flyer material (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Street Homeless Selective Enforcement Experience Survey (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Shelter and KYR flyers, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - "Representing Ourselves From the Grassroots" Film Festival and Training Conference, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Financial information, 2010-2011 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - General Welfare Project (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Welfare Warrior Research Collaborative, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - General WWRC, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Planning Meeting Notes (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - WWRC Survey material, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Survey outreach (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - "Welfare Made A Difference", 2004 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Storytelling, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Jay's work plan, notes and files (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Coalition CAG Summit, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - CHAMPS (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Coordinator's Report, agendas, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - QEJ Information and notes (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - CUNY Survey, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Bower Mission Women's Center, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Shelter safety programs and Local Law 3 papers, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Trans Homelessness Forum, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Resource papers, 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - QEJ sign-in sheets, 2007-2010 (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
  - QEJ and Welfare Warriors surveys (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - QEJ certificates of completion, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Outreach materials (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - YWCA, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - QEJ surveys (Box 9, Folder 10-11)
  - Welfare Warriors retreat meetings and notes, budgets and studies, 2006-2008 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Welfare Warriors survey information (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - The Low Income LGBT and Gender Nonconforming Peoples' Survey (Box 13, Folder 11-13)
  - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Cards (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - QEJ information and Pledge of Commitment (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Large notepad meeting sheets (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Series VII. Students, Volunteer, and Intern Program
  Among the job descriptions and reports about students, volunteers, and interns are information about a QEJ transgender meeting, and notes from a 1999 QEJ network meeting, prior to QEJ’s founding.
  - Grant information, 2008-2011 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - QEJ trans meeting information (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Legal Aid Society, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - NGLTF Consultant Agreements (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Summer intern report, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Volunteer forms (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Homelessness forum (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Amazing Queer Race sign-in, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Shelter Facilitator training materials, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - QEJ Supervision (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - JT Education plan (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - QEJ Staff Meeting, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Doyin, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Caterers (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Reina, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Job descriptions, SEED Report, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - First public work and meeting for QEJ network, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - QEJ supervision report, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Doyin supervision (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Debanuj supervision, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Shelter organization (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Travel/trips, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Volunteer forms (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Series VIII. Publicity
  The brochures, fliers, booklets, and posters designed to share information about the Shelter Safety Welfare Warriors, the Amazingly Queer Race for Economic Justice, and other projects, as well as articles about QEJ and one folder on QEJ’s history. The folder “Why Welfare Reform is a Queer Issue” includes materials from 1996-1999, prior to QEJ’s founding.
  Among the posters are:“Miss Jay Toole: Building for Social Justice,” "No Human is Illegal," "Sex Worker Visions," "End Eviction Orders!" "Welfare Made a Difference," handmade signs and posters, and a plastic QEJ sign.
  - Pamphlets, fliers, and booklets (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Amazingly Queer Race planning book (from binder), 2011 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - QEJ Support Group Feedback, 2004-2007 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - QEJ History (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Building a Queer Left, 2000-2004 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Amazingly Queer Race folder packet (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Why Welfare Reform is a Queer Issue, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Welfare Reform, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - City Limits article, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Speaking About Economic Justice, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Social Security Panel: Creating Change, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - DASIS Letter, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Planet Out article, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - QEJ stickers and cards (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Welfare Warriors research collaborative (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Shelter Safety Welfare Warriors (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - WWRC Attendance, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - WWRC information, 2007-2009 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Articles, 2001, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - "Welfare Made a Difference" and "Gay City: Vol. 3 No. 319" posters, 2004 (Folder 1)
  - "They take you in the morning, they will be coming for us at night" poster (Folder 1)
  - "Tales of the Waria" movie poster (Folder 1)
  - Miss Jay Toole: Building for Social Justice poster (Folder 1)
  - "No Human is Illegal" poster (Folder 1)
  - Council of the City of New York proclamation to QEJ (Folder 1)
  - Two vinyl banners banners ("Queers for Economic Justice," carried in marches and parades; "Beyond Same-Sex Marriage"); one rolled vinyl banner ("QUIR: Queer Immigrant Rights Project") (Folder 2)
  - "Sex Worker Visions" poster, 2006 (Folder 3)
  - QEJ plastic sign (Folder 3)
  - Event fliers (Folder 3)
  - "A New Queer Agenda" poster (Folder 3)
  - "A Time for Revolutionary Change" poster, 2005 (Folder 3)
  - "End Eviction Orders!" (Folder 3)
  - "Gay Seniors in New York City" informational poster (Folder 3)
  - Barack Poster (Folder 3)
  - Pastor Martin Niemoller quote poster (Folder 3)
  - Handmade signs and posters remembering individuals who had died, and messages including "Silence = Death" "Queer the Mind" and "Don't Deny It, Stonewall was a Riot." (Folder 4)
  - Planning Calendar (Dry Erase), 2012 (Folder 5)
- Series IX. Publications, Packets, and General Information
  - We Love Retail Workers packet (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - A Better Balance packet (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Living Wage NYC packet (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Causes in Common packet (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Equality and Justice for Children of Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and/or Transgender Parent/s packet (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Africans in America packet (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - In The News (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - A Different Vision of Activism (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Corporate Influence over LGBT Agenda (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Meeting minutes, general QEJ information (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Pamphlets and publications (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Pamphlets and publications (Box 10, Folder 1-6)